Guide to the Gerim M. Panarity Papers 1911-1985
University of Chicago Library
- Series VII: Oversized Materials
  This series is made up largely of newspapers and newspaper clippings, mainly on the subject of Albania, as well as maps, images and Panarity's scrapbook. Materials in this series range from 1911 to 1985. A number of the newspapers included here are printed in Albanian. Manuscripts for some of the published articles by Gerim Panarity in this series can be found in Series II. Additional material on both Dielli and the Orthodox Church in America can be found in Series IV. Images in this series have been removed from Series V.
  - Newspaper clippings of articles by Gerim Panarity, 1958-1971 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, 1938-1961 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings, Albania, USSR, Albanian-Americans, 1949-1970 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings, Albania and Albanians in America, 1938-1989 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Dielli, 1914-1938 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Dielli, single issues, 1937-1979 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Dielli, March 9, 1966, memorial for Bishop Fan S. Noli (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - The Trumpet of Croya, No. 1, March 20, 1911 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Telegraf, Nr. 2, August 14, 1926 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - "The Fundamental and Essential Values of Islam," insert, Mansfield News-Journal, January 28, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Shqiptari, June-July 1957 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Digest of Shqiptari i Lire, June 1958-April 1960 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Sbqipëria e Re, Vol. IX Nr. 10, October 1959 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - L’Albanie Libre, July 10, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Pages from Liria, February 4, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Dielli i Shqperise Ethnike, June-August 1979 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Maps of Albania, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Proclamation of Albanian Independence Day for the Commonwealth of Massachusetts, 1958 & 1959 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Ephemera, the Orthodox Church in America, 1968-1984 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - The Vineyard/The Vine, publication of the Albanian Archdiocese – Orthodox Church in America, 1980-1985 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Prints of portraits, King Zog and Queen Geraldine, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Photo, Pan-Albanian Federation 50th Anniversary Banquet in Honor of Bishop Fan S. Noli, September 3, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Print, statue of Scanderbeg, ca. 1968 (Box 13, Folder 23)